But here at KPU, all these gaps are filled with
how I am as a teacher and educator, how I talk to people, how children learn
And how to work with teaching different kinds in different forms.
We also have ensemble management here at the School of Music
And that was one of the reasons actually that I chose KPU here at the Music University in Malmö.
One day you sit in seminars and discuss literature and the other day you have to play electric guitar or drums.
It's simply a good mix.
My study is about group creation, so here to compose in groups.
I have a professional life behind me and an artistry, while I have pedagogy.
I can work at an aesthetic gym for now I have to rate.
So I feel it's a width